http://www.protegrity.com/legal-notice?hsLang=en

Protegrity | Legal Notice
Products
Why Protegrity
Our unique data security technologies are built for today's data-driven businesses.
Support
Click to toggle site search.
Legal / Privacy Notice
Overview:
Welcome to the Web Site located at “Protegrity.com” (the “Site”). This Site is owned and operated by Protegrity USA, Inc., its parents and affiliates (“Protegrity,” “we” or “us”) intended to furnish visitors, individually and/or on behalf of its respective employer (“you”) with general information on Protegrity and its products and services.
Protegrity’s mission is to provide visitors with a comprehensive online resource for information about our data-privacy products and services.
Certain statements made on this Site may be forward-looking in nature. Any statements that are not statements of historical fact should be considered forward-looking statements. While every effort has been made to offer current and accurate information, errors can occur. Furthermore, this Site may contain reference to certain laws and regulations. Laws and regulations will change over time and should be interpreted only in light of particular circumstances. Nothing on this Site serves as a substitute for appropriate professional consultation as to legal, insurance, accounting or other professional opinions.
We at Protegrity care deeply about privacy, security, and online safety, all of which are a significant part of our essential mission: to protect users of our products and services from the risks of theft, disruption, and unauthorized access to their online information and activities. Accordingly, this policy is designed to inform you about how we collect, use, and share your personal information, which relates to information we obtain from individuals through our websites, services and products. In using our Site and engaging with us relating to our business, products and services you acknowledge that you have read this notice and understand its contents. We may update this notice, or other privacy notices that we establish, at any time as we deem appropriate to reflect those changes. It is important that you check back from time to time and make sure that you have reviewed the most current version of this notice.
Content:
All trademark, service marks, trade names, trade logos and images are registered and/or common law trademarks and service marks of Protegrity shall remain Protegrity’s property.
Disclaimer:
THE SITE AND INFORMATION THEREWITH IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND, TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, PROTEGRITY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. PROTEGRITY SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR CLAIMS RELATED TO THE SITE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO INCIDENTIAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, EVEN IF YOU OR YOUR REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR CLAIMS.
Protegrity further disclaims and does not represent or warrant that the Site will operate without interruption, errors, defects, bugs or viruses, or that any such defects on the Site will be corrected. This Site may be modified from time to time without notice.
Third Party Web Sites:
Certain links on this Site lead to servers maintained by individuals or organizations over which Protegrity has no control. Protegrity makes no representations or warranties regarding the accuracy or any other aspect of the information located on such servers and are not responsible for the content, privacy practices, or use of any websites that are not affiliated with Protegrity. Linked websites may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit those websites.
Forums and Public Communication:
This Site may from time to time contain threaded discussion groups, bulletin boards and chat rooms (“Bulletin Boards”). Unless Protegrity specifically is identified as the author of a message, the responsibility for any opinions, advice, statements or other information contained in any messages posted or transmitted by any third party on this Site resides solely with the author.
Why Do We Collect Information and Data:
We rely on a wide variety of information to run our business. In some instances, this information may include data that could be used to identify a particular individual. There are multiple reasons why we collect such information. Some of the reasons include to: provide products and services; allow you to download and purchase products and services; personalize and manage our relationship with you; investigate, respond to and manage inquiries; allow for job applications and employment; and provide materials relating to our products and services.
Collection of Personal Information:
In some circumstances, Protegrity may request personal information from you that you may regard as private or sensitive, like your name, e-mail address, company name, company position, resume or telephone number (“Personal Information”). Your response to these inquiries is voluntary and you decide how much information you share with us. By voluntarily providing Protegrity with your Personal Information, you consent to Protegrity using this Personal Information to establish service or to provide you with the information, materials or related information that you request (collectively, “Services and Materials”), as well as Protegrity utilizing such Personal Information to run standard web analytics through use of anonymized user statistics for purposes of understanding and optimizing web usage.
You represent and warrant that any information (Personal Information or otherwise) you provide to Protegrity shall not include any information that actually or potentially infringes or misappropriates any intellectual property right of any third party or violates the privacy rights of any third party or violates any applicable law.
Ways Protegrity Collects and Uses Your Personal Information
Job Applications: If you are responding to a job application, you may provide us with a copy of your resume or other relevant information. We may use this information for the purpose of assessing your application. We may also keep this information on file to contact you about future opportunities, unless you ask us to remove your information from our systems. Further if you are extended a job opportunity we may keep this information to use for employment purposes.
Partner Portal: As a partner you may be given access to our partner portal, accordingly, if you are a partner you may visit our partner portal. We may use the information a partner provides us for partner relationship management, to provide partners with any information or related materials requested, and marketing.
Customer Portal: As a customer you may be given access to our partner portal, accordingly, if you are a customer you may visit our customer portal. We may use the information a customer provides us for customer relationship management, to provide products and other related documentation and materials, and support services.
Account Management: If you purchase products and/or services from us, we may use your contact details for the purposes of providing customer support and account management; billing and order processing; verifying usage of the products and services in accordance with the terms and conditions of you respective agreement with us; and contacting you regarding any license expiry, renewal and other related notices.
Marketing: Protegrity may contact you from time to time in order to provide you with information about products and services that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of any and all marketing materials to which you have signed up for at any time by clicking on the respective link provided in all marketing materials, or by contacting the below e-mail address.
Security Measures:
We will take reasonably appropriate measures to help prevent or mitigate unlawful or unauthorized processing of Personal Information, and against the accidental loss of, or damage to, Personal Information. We use administrative, organizational, technical and physical safeguards to protect the Personal Information we collect and process. Our security controls are designed to maintain an appropriate level of data confidentiality, integrity and availability and test our website, systems and other assets for security vulnerabilities.
Data Use and Data Transfer:
Protegrity’s corporate office is in the United States, and we have operations and affiliates throughout the world. As such, we and our affiliates may transfer your Personal Information to, or access it in, jurisdictions that may not provide equivalent levels of data protections as your home jurisdiction. We will take steps to ensure that your Personal Information receives an adequate level of protection in the jurisdictions in which we process it. We use this Personal Information solely for legitimate business purposes and only to the extent necessary, share your Personal Information to our affiliates, agents, independent contractors, and authorized resellers who provide services for us and you and provide guidance and assistance on the Services and Materials.
Compliance with Laws; Restrictions on Use and Transfer:
To the extent Protegrity processes your Personal Information in the course of providing Services and Materials, Protegrity will do so for a limited and specific purposes acting on behalf of you and in accordance with information protection laws. Additionally, Protegrity (i) shall not use, further disclose or transfer Personal Information other than as permitted or required to provide Services and Materials to you or as required by information protection laws; (ii) shall ensure that each employee, agent, subcontractor and any authorized third party is advised of and complies with the provisions hereof regarding the privacy and security of Personal Information; and (iii) shall not otherwise disclose, use, sell, transfer or rent such Personal Information to any third party or parties (including any subcontractor) without the prior express written approval of you.
Protegrity shall obtain all necessary permits and comply with information protection laws governing the privacy, security and trans-border transfers of Personal Information, as applicable to the Services and Materials provided by Protegrity including, but not limited to, compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and its requirements related to verifiable consent, parental consent, recordkeeping, data protection by design, data protection impact assessments, and any other requirements relating to providing notice and obtaining consent to collect and/or transfer Personal Information, data localization and cookies under information protection laws.
Breaches and Unauthorized Disclosures/Sharing:
Protegrity maintains an incident response plan that addresses security incident handling. Protegrity agrees to provide you (and, as applicable, the requisite authorities) without undue delay, but in no event later than seventy-two (72) hours of identification of a confirmed incident, written notice of any security incident that involves, the unauthorized access, use or disclosure of your Personal Information. Such notice shall summarize in reasonable detail to the best of its knowledge the likely consequences of such breach or unauthorized use or disclosure of or access to, Personal Information, including where possible, the categories and approximate number of personal records concerned, and the corrective action taken or to be taken by Protegrity including, where appropriate, measures to mitigate its possible adverse effects.
IP Addresses:
An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are using your browser on the Internet. The servers that operate Protegrity’s website automatically identify a computer by its IP address. If Protegrity determines, in good faith, that you have used the service to menace, threaten, harass, intimidate or otherwise deceptively pose as another person, your actions will be investigated, and your IP address may be disclosed to the recipient of any e-mail, their legal counsel or representatives, and law enforcement officials as part of such investigation.
Cookies:
A “cookie” is a small piece of data stored on a user’s browser and contains non-personally identifiable information about the user. When you visit the Site, Protegrity may place a “cookie” on your browser in order to improve your experience by recognizing when you visit the website in order to allow Protegrity to optimize the information presented based on your demonstrated areas of interest. Cookies may also be used to compile information about website usage. This information can be used to enhance the content of the website and make your experience more informative. If you subsequently provide us with Personal Information, we will associate any cookies on your browser with that information such that you will no longer be an anonymous visitor to the Site, unless otherwise requested by you.
Collecting Domain Information:
Protegrity also collects domain information as part of its analysis of the use of this site. This data enables us to become more familiar with which customers visit our site, how often they visit and what parts of the site they visit most often. Protegrity uses this information to improve its web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part.
Disclosure to Third Parties:
Protegrity will not provide other third parties with individual or aggregate information about visitors to our site. We do not sell, rent or market personal data about you to third parties.
Data Retention:
The time periods for which we retain your Personal Information depend on the purposes for which we use it. Protegrity will keep your Personal Information for as long as you are a registered subscriber or user of our products or services or for as long as we have another business purpose to do so and, thereafter, for no longer than is required or permitted by law, or Protegrity’s record retention policy, as reasonably necessary for internal reporting and reconciliation purposes, or to provide you with feedback or information you might request. The information we collect may be stored and processed in servers in the United States and wherever Protegrity has servers around the globe.
Protegrity’s obligation to protect your Personal Information will continue until all your Personal Information has been permanently and completely destroyed or deleted, including from any back-up or other databases.
Assistance to You:
You have the right to direct and restrict Protegrity in connection with the collection, use, disclosure and retention of such Personal Information. You have the right to request a copy of your Personal Information Protegrity maintains, and may request such information by contacting the below contact. You may revoke your consent, review and correct, and request that we delete your Personal Information by contacting us through the e-mail address provided in the below “Contact Information” Section. When you do so, please provide your name and a clear description of the information you wish to have revised or deleted. Protegrity shall respond to any and all such requests for relating to rights of access, rectification, erasure, restriction of processing and data portability within one (1) month of their receipt.
To the extent you determine that it is required under application information protection laws to conduct a data protection impact assessment and/or prior consultation with a supervisory authority in connecting with processing that is likely to result in a high risk to the rights and freedoms of natural persons, Protegrity shall provide you with assistance in ensuring compliance with such obligations.
If you in good faith believe that Protegrity has not handled your Personal Information in accordance with the requirements of the GDPR or other application information protection laws, then please contact the e-mail address provided in the “Contact Information” Section.
California Privacy Rights
California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from Protegrity once annually, without charge, a list of third parties (if any) to whom we have disclosed their Personal Information in the prior year, as well as the type of Personal Information disclosed to such third parties. If you are a California resident and would like to make such request, please submit your request to the below listed e-mail address.
Contact Information:
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Legal/Privacy Notice, or would like to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by e-mail at privacy@protegrity.com and a member of our team will get back to you.
Products
Why Protegrity
Vaultless Tokenization
Data Discovery
Professional Services
Data Management
Data Protectors
Security Gateways
Copyright © 2020. Protegrity USA, Inc. All rights reserved.
Contact Us|
Follow Us
Legal and Privacy Notice
